烈日没供出来什么吧
Sunshine keeping quiet?
根据我们的线报  她自从昨天被捕之后
Our source confirms she hasn't said a word
一个字都没说
since her arrest yesterday.
不过韦斯特队长不肯罢休
But Captain West won't stop making noise.
他执着于将你和
He is obsessed with connecting you
烈日  致命紫光  还有光博士联系起来
to Sunshine, Ultraviolet, and Dr. Light.
他的想法很快就无关紧要了
That won't matter much longer.
我们的客人什么时候到
When will our guest arrive?
多谢你在临时通知下赶来
Thanks for coming on short notice.
这是你的目标
This is your target.
请杀掉他
Kill him, please.
闪 电 侠
第六季
第十六集
准备  开始
And...go.
是某种地图吗
Like a map of some kind?
-不是  -是个通量电容器
- No. - That's a flux capacitor.
等  不对
Hold--no.
-不对  就是这样  没错  -不对
- No, that's good, yeah. - No.
他们肯定猜不到
They are not gonna get this.
-这个是  -就画好了  等下  好了
- Oh, this is-- - Okay, hold on. All right.
我是打算画埃菲尔铁塔的
Okay, it was gonna be the Eiffel Tower.
真是的
Oh, damn.
确实很像埃菲尔铁塔
That looks just like the Eiffel Tower.
-看起来像信号塔  -我还真画过类似的
- It looks like a radio tower. - I actually does stuff like that.
我得接这个电话
Oh, I got to take this.
你好  大卫
Hey, David.
乔  我知道你认为
Joe, I know you think we can tie
这个杀手烈日和卡弗必定有关系
this assassin Sunshine to Carver,
但是她不肯招供
but she is just not talking.
好的  那让我审她试试
Okay, so let me take a crack at it.
实际上  我要你先别管这个案子了
Actually, I need you to take a step back from this case.
你太贴近这个案子了
You're too close to it.
况且  你现在是队长
Besides, you're the Captain now.
大卫  正因我贴近  我才能让她开口
David, it's because I'm close that I can rattle her.
拜托了  没有其他人能做到
Come on, there's nobody else that can do this.
好吧
Okay.
好的
Oh, okay.
是卡弗的案子吗
Was that the Carver case?
-是的  -我能帮上忙吗
- Yeah. - How can I help?
你要节省自己的能量
You just conserve your energy.
如果我有任何需要会打给你的
I'll call you if I need anything.
我得走了  各位  保重
I got to go, guys. Take care.
-好的  再见  -再见
- Oh, okay, bye. - Bye.
我想我找到了离开这里的方法
I think I found a way out of here.
什么  怎么找到的
What? How?
我是从专注于这些显示屏开始的
I started focusing on the monitors.
一开始尝试时  我看不清上面的内容
At first, when I tried, I couldn't read them.
我会  出现头疼
I would get all of these, um--these headaches.
-是的  -但是今天
- Yeah. - But today...
它们开始聚焦了
it started to come into focus...
非常清晰
perfectly clear.
你开始适应这个地方了
You're adapting to this place.
我读过你的理论
I read your theory
提到如果一个人的分子结构变得不稳定了
that says that someone could pass through the mirror
他可以穿越过这些镜子
if their molecular structure was destabilized?
是的
Yes.
如果我可以联系上我的丈夫
Well, if I could just contact my husband,
我想他能够帮助我们
I think he might be able to help us.
伊娃  我丈夫巴里·艾伦
Eva, my husband, Barry Allen,
就是闪电侠
is The Flash.
什么
What?
用他的神速  我想他能将我们从这里穿越出去
And with his speed, I think he could phase us out of here.
如果他的瞬间速度
If his instantaneous velocity
与分形表面的极限产生联动
correlates with the limit of the fractal surface,
他就会变成没有实际形体了
then...then he'll become intangible.
所以  是可行的
So...it could work!
是的  是的  我
Yes! Yes, I...
只是  我需要恢复
I just--I need to recharge.
我一早上都在控制镜子
I've been controlling the mirror all morning,
我已经精疲力尽了
and I'm--I'm exhausted.
是的  你好好休息
Yeah, um, take all the time you need.
我会  继续尝试破译
I will, um, keep trying to decipher more.
好的  你继续
Yeah. You--you do that.
你的方向是正确的
You're--you're on the right path.
好的
Yeah.
她刚刚所做的正如我所预料
She just did exactly what I knew she would do.
她甚至将她丈夫的真实身份告诉我了
She even told me the truth about her husband.
伊娃  乔·韦斯特仍然在
Eva, Joe West is still looking
调查你丈夫的活动
into your husband's activities.
他知道黑洞
He knows about Black Hole.
那用不了多久  巴里·艾伦就会帮他
Then it's only a matter of time before Barry Allen helps him.
你有新任务了
You have a new mission.
闪电侠要失去神速力了
The Flash is losing his speed.
榨干他剩下的速度
Drain him of the rest.
你为什么担心闪电侠
Why do you care about The Flash?
我不担心  我担心的是我丈夫
I don't. I care about my husband.
闪电侠不能把他从我身边抢走
The Flash is not gonna take that away from me.
成功是无疑的
Success is assured.
我收到你的短信  怎么了
I got your text. What's up?
凯里·马西森  这么多红线吗
Okay, Carrie Mathison, red string much?
自从苏失踪后  我一直在追踪她的下落
I've been tracking Sue since she disappeared.
她突袭了五个地方的五家银行
She's hit five banks in five locations.
在她突袭时候  每一个地方都正好
Every single one of them was doing some schmoozy cocktail party
在搞休闲鸡尾酒会
when she did it.
当大家都在品尝香槟
And while everybody was sipping champagne
吃着昂贵晚餐时  突然间
and eating an overpriced meal, bam.
服务器机房就被入侵了
Server rooms get hacked.
我知道这表情
I know that look.
你找到了她的下一个目标
You found her next target.
我当然找到了她的下一个目标
Of course I found her next target.
第一国家中城银行
投资者午宴
第一国家中城银行将要给他们最大的客户
The First National CC Bank is holding an investors' brunch
举办投资者午宴
for their biggest clients.
符合苏的作案手法
Fits Sue's M.O. to a T.
所以我需要你的帮忙  我的朋友
Now, here's where you come in, my friend.
我需要一个能设网帮忙抓住她的黑客
I need a hacker who can set up a net to help catch her,
一个能监控安全录像的人
somebody who can monitor the security feed,
一个懂得带宽  知道二进制的人
somebody who speaks bandwidth and knows binary.
我想你不知道黑客的运作方式
I'm not sure you know how hacking works.
拜托
Please.
我看过电影《电子情书》好几次了
I've seen "You've Got Mail" several times.
但我知道
But I know
你一直在研究人造神速力
you've been working on the Artificial Speed Force, so...
是的  但我整天都在模拟
I have, but I'm running simulations all day--
那些模拟不需要我时刻盯着
simulations I don't need to be there for.
这样吧
Look, here's the deal.
我知道这件案子对你来说有多不容易
I know how hard this case has been on you.
我一开始就应该帮你的
I should've been there to help you from the beginning.
所以
So...
所以你要帮我吗
So you're in?
有华夫饼吃吗
Will there be waffles?
最好有华夫饼
There better be waffles.
不不不不
No, no, no, no!
好的  谢谢你
Okay. Thank you.
太疯狂了
It was crazy.
车子好像自己在加速一样
It was like it was accelerating by itself.
我知道说了你也不信
I mean, I know you won't believe this,
但感觉就像是我在开车时
but it was like somebody cut the brakes
有人剪断了刹车线
while I was driving.
有可能会这样吗
Is that even possible?
我不知道  我会查清楚的
I-I don't know. I'll find out.
-你确定你没事吗  -我没事
- Are you sure you're okay? - I'm fine.
卡弗才是你们要担心的
It's Carver that needs to worry.
你觉得是卡弗搞的鬼
You think Carver's the one behind this?
他知道我打败了他其中一个杀手
Well, he knows I took down one of his assassins,
米莉·罗林斯  外号烈日
Millie Rawlins, AKA Sunshine.
他还知道我负责反腐调查组
And he knows I'm the lead on the RICO case
我们正在调查他
we're building against him.
如果这是真的
Well, if that's true,
我们必须要给你安排证人保护计划
we have to get you in witness protection.
你现在出外勤不安全  乔
You're just not safe out here, Joe.
大卫  我哪也不去
David, I'm not going anywhere.
如果卡弗要来找我
Look, if Carver is coming after me,
说明他害怕了
that means he is scared.
害怕的人会怎么样  他们会犯错
What do scared people do? They make mistakes.
我们要好好利用这一点
We need to take advantage of that.
好吧  好吧
Fine. Fine.
我会一如既往全力支持你  乔
You have my complete support, Joe, as always.
但如果发生什么事  我绝对不会原谅自己
But if anything happens, I'll never forgive myself.
我要去见罗林斯
I need to go talk to Rawlins.
投资者午宴正在如火如荼地进行中
Okay, the investors' brunch is in full swing.
让我们看到服务器机房里的情况
Now, you go get us eyes on that server room.
我要去小解
I got to tinkle.
我听到自己的话了
Yeah, I heard what I said.
好
Okay.
医生来了
The doctor is in.
喊"啊"
Say, "Ah!"
什么
What?
你管这叫加密方案
You call this an encryption scheme?
我一只手被绑在背后都能破解它
I could do this with one hand tied behind my back.
证明一下
Prove it.
早上好
Uh, good morning.
不用管我  我只是在进行常规软件更新
Don't mind me. I'm just doing a routine software update.
请问我能收回我的手吗
Can I have my hand back, please?
你真会打扮...  作为技术人员来说
You dress well... for tech support.
我具备良好的职业操守
I have good work ethic.
有意思
Funny.
看起来你当时在篡改
It looked like you were tampering
这台设备的安全系统
with the facility's security system,
而不是在修理它
not repairing it.
篡  篡  篡改吗
Tam--tamp--tampering?
你是说这个吗
Oh, you--you mean all this?
是的  那些全部
Yes, all of that.
不  我  这是我们按照合规程序
No, no, I'm--it's-- this is a procedure we follow
来确保你的资金安全
to make sure that your money's secure.
也就是说  你的资金安全
That is, if the safety of your money
对于你来说是否很重要  女士
is important to you, Miss...?
詹纽瑞·加罗尔女士
Ms. January Galore.
我的资金安全对我来说非常重要
And the safety of my money is very important to me.
我相信是的
I'm sure it is.
所以这小绿灯有什么作用
So what do those little green lights do?
这  这  这绿光
The--the--the--the-- the green lights.
它们  它们不重要
They are--they are not important.
我其实已经搞定了
I'm actually all done here.
好好享用华夫饼
Um, enjoy the waffles.
我会的
Oh, I will.
我感觉这里只有苹果馅
I think they only have apple fritters here.
我们同步了吗
Are we live?
是的  我们同步了  我们能看到了
Yeah, we're live. We got eyes.
虽然我们差点没有成功
We almost didn't get them, though.
我遇到了一个捐赠者  富有的英国女士
I ran into one of the donors-- some rich British lady.
她的名字叫什么来着  六月  四月
What was her name? June, April...
-四月·加罗尔  -慢着
- April Gabor. - Wait.
-詹纽瑞·加罗尔  -就是她
- January Galore? - That's the one.
情况不妙
That's not good.
她是我和巴里在米德韦城遇到的军火商
She's an arms dealer that Barry and I met in Midway City.
我不知道
I don't know.
她看起来挺吸引我的
She seemed kind of charming to me.
超级主动  但还是很迷人
Very forward, but charming nonetheless.
我们遇上麻烦了
Uh-oh. We're in trouble.
监控信号没有了
The security feeds are dead.
服务器在第五楼
Servers are on the fifth floor.
我们走
Let's go.
这是什么  这是什么
What is that? What is that?
完美的伪装
The perfect disguise.
伪...
A disg--
我没有胃口了
I think I just lost my appetite.
滑头  想我了吗
Hi, Slick. You miss me?
几乎和我想念弗雷德里克一样多
Almost as much as I miss Fredrico,
我的绦虫
my tapeworm.
你好  苏  或是詹纽瑞
Hello, Sue. Or is it January?
我还能说什么
What can I say?
抵押贷款债券
Collateralized loan obligations
真的极其诱人
are deliciously robust.
尽管...
Although...
不及穿礼服的你一半诱人
Not half as delicious as you in a tux.
还在干老本行吗  偷钻石和珍珠
Still up to your old tricks? Swiping diamonds and pearls?
你喜欢普林斯  我也是
Oh, you like Prince? Me too.
是的  我也是
Yes! Me three.
我叫西斯科  顺便一提
I'm Cisco, by the way.
我们之前在那里见过...
We met back when you were...
詹纽瑞·加罗尔
January Galore.
你的口音听起来真棒
That was an excellent accent, by the way.
-你有训练过吗  -谢谢你
- Do you have any training? - Oh, thank you.
-我高中在国外读书  -肯定是在伦敦
- I did my senior year abroad. - London, no doubt.
-是在意大利  实际上  -她很酷  你很酷
- Oh, Italy, actually. - She fancy. You fancy.
-谢谢  -好了
- Yeah, thank you. - Okay!
苏  你无路可逃了  你要完蛋了
Sue, you're trapped, and you're going down.
实际上  我要上去了
Oh, actually, I'm going up.
你看到了吗
Ah. Did you see that?
-你在...  -你看到了吗
- What do you-- - Did you see that?
糟了  该死
Shoot. Damn it!
糟糕
Uh-oh. Dibs.
如果这个东西是她用的
If this is what she used,
她可以访问所有银行的储蓄
she has access to all the bank's financial holdings.
那个
Oh, well...
也就
It's only several...
几十亿美元
billion...
而已
dollars.
中城警局
米莉·罗林斯
Millie Rawlins.
这个人曾经为约瑟夫·卡弗工作
This man--he worked for Joseph Carver.
这就是那些让卡弗失望的人的下场
This is what happens to those who fail Carver.
这可以激励其他人成功
Incentive for the rest of us to succeed.
但是你没成功
But you didn't succeed.
所以下一个死的可能是你
So that probably means you're next.
听着 我可以保护你
Now, look, I can offer you protection.
但仅此一次
But this is a one-time deal.
你有兴趣吗
Are you interested?
没有  谢谢
No, thanks.
只有一种办法可以让人
I mean, the only way somebody could accelerate the car
在汽车加速的同时切断刹车
and simultaneously cut the brakes
那就是在汽车的发动机里
is from inside the car's engine, which is...
很明显这里装不下人
I mean, obviously no person could fit inside there.
雷·帕尔默能进去
Well, Ray Palmer could.
但他不会去杀人或搞破坏
Only he's not a murderous, sabotaging type.
如果是一个可以挤进狭小空间的超能力者
How about a meta-human who can squeeze into tight places?
他喜欢亲眼看着受害者遭到痛苦
Likes to watch his victims suffering up close.
布娃娃
Rag Doll.
好了
Now...
米莉·罗林斯
what would...
陆军中尉
First Lieutenant Millie Rawlins,
曾经从叛乱的劳改营中
a soldier who had rescued 14 friendlies
营救出十四名友军的士兵
from an insurgent labor camp,
她会怎样看待如今的你
think of what you've become now?
你曾经荣誉等身
You were honorable.
功绩勋章
Legion of Merit.
勇气勋章
Medal of Valor.
米莉
Millie,
你要拿回这些荣誉
restore that honor.
帮我阻止约瑟夫·卡弗  免得为时太晚
Help me stop Joseph Carver before it's too late.
趴下  趴下
Get down! Get down!
怎么回事
What the hell?
乔  乔
Joe, Joe, hey.
对不起
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
我没事  受伤都习惯了
I'm fine. I'm all bandaged up.
行了  乔  这是第二次了
All right, Joe. That's twice now.
这也是我第二次拿到健康证明
And that's twice I've gotten a clean bill of health.
好吧
All right.
等等  你要去哪
Wait, hold on. Where are you going?
巴里  我还是这次调查的负责人
Barry, I am still the lead on this investigation.
我差一点就能和罗林斯达成认罪协议
And I was this close to getting a deal
如果不是
with Rawlins if it wasn't--
他是危险的疯子  而且他盯上你了
He's a dangerous psycho, and he's got your number.
好吧  虽然我不想说出来
All right, look, I-I-I hate to say it,
但是  我说不准
but I-I don't know.
也许辛格说的是对的
It feels like maybe Singh was right.
你应该暂时放下这案子
And you should let this go for a while.
所以你现在让我不要调查案件了
Oh, so you're gonna take me off the case now.
不是  我只是想保护你的安全
No, I just--I'm trying to keep you safe, all right?
我现在的速度不足以让我保护你了
And I-I'm not fast enough to do that anymore.
看看你的胳膊
I mean, look at your arm.
巴里  我都这么接近了是不可能放弃的
Well, Barry, you know I'm not gonna stop if I'm this close.
我明白  但是在我阻止布娃娃之前
Look, I get it, but will you please just stay here
你能不能留在尖端实验室
at S.T.A.R. Labs, at least until I've stopped Rag Doll?
行
Fine.
乔
Joe.
-你怎么了  -没事
- Hey, you okay? - I'm good.
-怎么回事  -有枪战
- What happened? - There was gunfire.
我的速度不足以拦下所有子弹
And I wasn't fast enough to stop all the bullets.
他没事  但是他受伤是我的错
He's--he's fine, but it's my fault that he got hurt.
巴里  你的速度
Barry, your speed.
-越来越不乐观了  -我知道
- It's getting worse. - I know.
你有什么对策吗
But what are you gonna do?
我要用面部识别算法
I'm gonna use facial-recognition algorithms
和超能力者追踪器
and meta-human trackers.
就算用尽尖端实验室所有的资源
I'm gonna find Rag Doll and stop him
我也要找到布娃娃
if I have to use every last resource
然后阻止他
at S.T.A.R. Labs to do it.
除了最重要的
Except the one that counts.
巴里  你答应过我会保护他的安全
Barry, you promised me that you would keep him safe.
-我知道  -我不能失去我父亲
- I know. - I can't lose my dad.
你不会的  我发誓
You won't. I swear.
我
I...
请进
Come in.
当我的私人保镖说我有来客时
When my private security said I had a guest,
我最想不到的就是你
the last person I expected to see was
乔·韦斯队长
Captain Joe West.
我想你来这是有紧急警务吧
I suppose you're here on urgent police business.
私事
Personal.
你想杀我的时候都这么说
You made it that way when you tried to kill me...
两次都是
twice.
我不知道你在说什么
I have no idea what you're talking about.
彼得·梅克尔  布娃娃
Peter Merkel, Rag Doll--
上次他被看到是闯入麦克洛奇技术公司时
Last he was seen was breaking into McCulloch Technologies.
大概是一年前
That was about a year ago.
是的
Yes.
我们最近有很多安全问题
We have had a number of security issues lately,
我相信你知道
as I'm sure you're aware.
是的  奇怪的是中城警局
Yeah, the strange thing is the CCPD
从没捉住过他
never apprehended him.
他就那么消失了
He just vanished...
直到今天
until today.
有关此事你知道什么吗
Do you know anything about that?
听起来你准备了
Sounds like you've crafted
一些关于我的有趣故事
some very interesting narratives
韦斯特队长
about me, Captain West.
甚至听起来像在说
It even sounds like you're saying I hired someone
我雇人从盒子里跳出来暗杀你
to pop out of a box to assassinate you.
我是说
I mean...
我没说
I didn't say
布娃娃是从盒子里蹦出来的
that Rag Doll popped out of a box.
该死
Damn.
我之前瞒得挺好的
And I was doing so well.
你可真讨厌  队长
You've been a pain in the ass, Captain.
你占用我太多的时间了
And you've taken up far too much of my time.
所以我给你个一次性的条件
So I'm gonna make you a one-time-only offer.
我取消梅克尔刺杀
I will call off Merkel,
你只需从那走出去
and all you have to do is walk out that door
再别来烦我
and leave me alone forever.
我要还价
I'll make a counteroffer.
你因试图谋杀辖区队长的罪名
You spend 80 years in Iron Heights
需在铁山监狱待八十年
for attempting to assassinate the precinct captain.
科技就是善变的情人
Technology is a fickle mistress.
录音已删除
局部的数据管理平台脉冲
A localized DMP pulse.
也是拥有
And one of the advantages
世上最先进科技公司的
of owning the most advanced technological institution
好处之一
in the world.
无论你认为我做了什么
Whatever you think I've done,
都比你想象的更糟
it's a million times worse.
我可以在任何地方消灭任何人
I can eliminate anyone, anywhere.
包括你
And that includes you...
还有你可爱的伴侣  霍尔顿女士
or your lovely companion, Ms. Horton...
甚至你们可爱的小宝宝
Even that precious little baby of yours.
你取掉你的徽章
You took your badge off
就那么走进去  知道可能发生什么
and just walked right in there knowing what could happen.
你到底在想什么
I--What the hell were you thinking?
你觉得我去卡夫的家
Do you think I went over to Carver's house
是为了逞英雄那一套
for some macho BS?
你知道我没那么骄傲
You know I'm not proud like that.
我只是害怕我不能保护我的家人
I was just terrified I can't protect my family.
但现在是你需要保护
But you're the one who needs protecting right now.
我不担心我自己  巴里
I'm not worried about me, Barry.
我不能失去塞西尔和詹娜
I can't lose Cecile and Jenna.
我们不能失去你  听着
And we can't lose you! Listen!
卡夫拥有无限的资源
Carver has unlimited resources, right?
先是光博士  然后是烈日
I mean, first it was Dr. Light, then it was Sunshine.
今天是布娃娃  明天
Today it's Rag Doll, and tomorrow...
谁知道呢
it's who knows?
现在如果我不能保护你
And now if I can't protect you...
你想让我做什么
What do you want me to do?
考虑下证人保护计划
Think about witness protection.
乔  你得活着
Joe, you need to stay alive.
参与五年投资
Committing to a five-year investment
能保证百分之五的收益  热那亚小姐
will guarantee you a 5% return, Miss Genoa.
为了安全起见  我们的服务器房
As for security, our server room
使用军用级别的合金钢进行加固
is reinforced with military-grade steel alloys.
听起来攻不可破
Hmm, sounds wonderfully impenetrable.
是的  不过没什么是攻不可破的
Yeah, but nothing is impenetrable.
不是吗  迪尔邦女士
Isn't that right, Ms. Dearbon?
迪尔邦
Dearbon?
你说你叫热那亚  意大利裔
You said your name was Genoa, like the Salami.
我该好好演下去的
她可没说实话
You know, she lied about that.
她就是这样  不过她确实人傻钱多
It's kind of her thing. She is stupid rich, though.
这么说的话...
Oh. In that case...
你们俩是怎么认识的  你们结婚了吗
How do you two know each other? Are you married?
恶心
Gross.
能不能让我们单独谈谈
Uh, do you mind excusing us for a moment?
我也想和我的这位朋友
I would love to speak to my friend
聊聊在此投资的事
about possibly investing here as well.
当然可以
By all means.
慢慢聊
Take your time.
斯利克...
So, Slick...
你是来伸张正义的吗
you here to make a super citizen's arrest?
我知道你是什么企图
I know what you're up to.
是吗
Really?
洗耳恭听
I'm all ears.
这里面是你父母的银行账户
The files on this are your parents' bank accounts.
他们每周都准时转账
They've been wiring money every week like clockwork
到一个加密的账户
to a coded account.
你的父母被人勒索了
Your parents are being extorted.
怎么  不反驳一下吗
What? No snarky comeback?
那就是我说对了
Oh. That means I'm right.
因此你想说什么
You going somewhere with this?
我猜勒索你父母的人
Well, my guess is that your parents are being blackmailed
就是我们上次见面时
by the same person who owns every single banking system
被你黑进账户的那个人
that you've hacked into since we last met
约瑟夫·卡夫
Joseph Carver.
当心点  斯利克
Careful, Slick.
你根本不是在偷窃
You weren't stealing anything
无论是巴黎  上海  还是中城
in Paris, Shanghai, or Central City.
你在调查卡夫
You were investigating Carver.
他一定是知道了他们什么不可告人的秘密
He must have found out their ugly little secret.
怎么  他们偷税漏税了吗
What, do they lie on their tax returns?
还是行贿才进的游艇俱乐部
They bribe their way into that yacht club?
够了
Enough.
无论你想对我怎样
Assume whatever you want about me,
都不要牵扯到我的父母
but don't do it about my parents.
他们是好人
They're good people.
那就让我帮你
Then let me help you.
我并不了解你
I barely know you.
重要的你都知道了
You know everything that matters.
声明一下
For the record,
我并不喜欢捉弄你
I didn't enjoy tricking you.
好吧  我是喜欢的
Okay, I enjoyed it.
但说实话  事后我觉得很糟糕
But honestly, I felt pretty crappy afterwards.
怎么这副表情
Why is that?
因为你是一个好人...
'Cause you are a good person...
像你父母一样
just like your parents.
你只是有些...问题
You just have some... issues.
你可真是正直  让人恶心
You're so decent. It's nauseating.
那你应该见见两年前的我
Oh, boy, you should've seen me about two years ago.
那时我可是个十足的混蛋
I was a, I was a real crap-bag.
不过你可能会很喜欢
Actually, you probably would have liked that, though.
不好说
I don't know.
你做的这些"好人好事"...
This whole good-guy thing you got going on...
还是可以接受的
It's...tolerable.
可以接受
Tolerable.
所以...
Which is why...
我要把这个给你
I'm giving you this.
仔细看
Look into that.
你会发现有趣的东西
You might find something interesting.
我就发现了
I did.
我刚和爱瑞丝通了电话
I just talked to Iris.
她说有人要杀韦斯特队长
She said someone tried to kill Captain West.
是的  约瑟夫·卡夫
Yeah. Joseph Carver.
我们该怎么办
So what do we do?
我派詹娜去保护她的姐姐  琼妮
Uh, I sent Jenna to stay with her sister, Joanie,
所以她很安全
so we know she's safe.
还有...
And, uh...
我也不知道
I don't know.
塞西尔  如果卡夫知道你在帮乔...
Cecile, if you're helping Joe and Carver finds out...
你觉得怎样  他也会来报复我吗
What do you think? He's gonna come after me, too?
即使他想  也要先过我这关
If he does, he'll have to go through me.
来
Come here.
还有我
Me too.
对不起  我忍不住偷听了
Sorry, I couldn't help but overhear.
但我是来保护大家安全的  你们觉得安全吗
But I'm here to help keep everyone safe. You feel safe?
我们很安全  但你不怎么安全
We're safe. You, not so much.
阿莱格拉  阿莱格拉
Allegra. Hey, Allegra.
别这样  别这样
Come on. Come on.
我要做什么才能弥补
Hey, what--what can I do to fix this?
因为我觉得很内疚
'Cause I-I feel terrible.
那我的感受呢
What about how I feel?
以前  很多人都说在乎我
I've been lied to before a lot
但其实都在骗我
by pretty much anyone who's ever said they cared about me.
现在你居然指望我笑着说一切都好
And now you expect me to smile and say it's all okay
就因为你觉得内疚
because you feel bad?
不  我...
No, I--
我该怎么办
What am I supposed to do?
走开
Walk away.
好极了
Great.
阿莱格拉
Allegra!
塞西尔·霍尔顿
受不了了  受不了了
It's too much. It's too much.
太痛苦了  太痛苦了
It's too much pain. It's too much pain.
你会受到
You will bring
很多折磨
so much suffering.
巴仔  布娃娃抓走了塞西尔  他发了这个过来
Bare, Rag Doll took Cecile. He sent this.
如此多美味的折磨
So much delicious suffering.
回头见  队长
See you soon, Captain.
好  我可以追踪塞西尔的手机
All right, I-I can track Cecile's phone,
但是  乔  他就想让你找到她
but, Joe, he wants you to find her,
就像他利用我引诱爱瑞丝一样  这是陷阱
just like he used me to lure Iris--it's a trap.
如果她有什么三长两短  都是我的错
If something happens to her, it's on me.
不  我们会把她救回来的
No, we're gonna bring her home.
-但你的神速怎么办  -别担心我的神速
- But what about your speed? - Don't worry about my speed.
我会尽一切所能  好吗
I'll do whatever I can, all right?
不保她安全我不罢休  走吧
I won't hold back until she's safe. Let's go.
-你没事吧  -我没事  我很好
- You okay? - I'm okay. I'm good.
乔  去找塞西尔  我来拖住他
Joe, find Cecile. I'll hold him off.
快去  队长  快去
Run, Captain. Run.
塞西尔  塞西尔
Cecile! Cecile!
宝贝
Babe!
宝贝  我来了
Babe. I'm coming.
好
Okay.
小心  小心  别碰我
Careful, careful. Don't touch me.
这是个压力炸弹
It's a pressure bomb.
如果减轻上面的重量  它就会爆炸
If it's not weighted down, it'll explode.
你怎么会知道
How do you know that?
他让我告诉你的
He told me to tell you.
好吧
Okay.
我看到你了
I see you.
错过我了
Missed me.
差不多了
Oh, almost.
越来越近了
Getting closer.
慢慢享受折磨吧
Suffer nice and slow.
乔·韦斯特队长
韦斯特队长  布娃娃来过这里
Captain West? Rag Doll was here.
对  我知道  他抓走了塞西尔
Yeah, I know. He took Cecile.
我现在跟她在一起
I'm here with her now.
听着  我需要你们帮忙拆除炸弹
Listen, I need your help defusing an explosive.
什么样的炸弹  队长
Uh, what kind of a device is it, Captain?
是一个M112型
Uh, it is a Michael 1-1-2
M112型C4组合块状爆破药包
C4组合块状
composition Charlie 4
爆破药包
block demolition charge.
C4块状爆破药包
C4 block demolition charge.
好  找到了
Yeah. Got it.
好  别紧张
Okay, so, easy.
打开外侧面板  你会看到四根电线
Open the outer panel. You're gonna see four wires.
拉出绿色的那根
Pull the green one.
里面不止四根线
There are more than four wires,
而且全是绿色的
and they're all green.
我来搞定
I got this.
怎么搞定  队长
But how? Captain--
好
Okay.
宝贝
Babe...
你记得在你堂兄婚礼上跳的那支舞吗
do you remember dancing at your cousin's wedding?
什么  我们一开始步调不一致
what, when you were stepping on my toes
你老在踩我脚那次吗
until we finally got in sync?
对  我们现在就要跳舞
Yeah, we're gonna do that now.
什么  不
What? No.
-不  -我们没有时间了
- No. - We do not have time.
-我不能让你这样做  -跟着我
- I can't let you do this. - Follow me.
-数到三  就换  好吗  -好
- On three, move, okay? - Okay.
一  二  三
One, two, three!
减少了一分钟
We lost a minute.
你无法让任何人受折磨了  梅克尔
You're not gonna make anyone suffer anymore, Merkel,
无论黑洞付了多少钱给你
no matter how much Black Hole's paying you.
付钱
Pay?
不在乎钱
Don't care about money.
如果你要杀乔不是为了钱
If you're not trying to kill Joe for money,
那你为什么这么做
why are you doing this?
解脱
Oh, release.
母亲死了  心脏病
Mother's dead. Heart attack.
没有人受折磨了
No one left to suffer now.
除了我自己
Except myself.
谢谢你  闪电侠  帮我受折磨
Thank you, Flash, for helping me suffer.
现在随时有可能
Any second now,
解脱就伴随着砰的一声
release comes with kaboom!
乔  你做了什么
Joe, what did you-- what did you do?
做了我必须要做的
What I had to do.
拜托你把塞西尔带离这里
Please get Cecile out of here now.
不  不  我不想离开你
No, no. I don't want to leave you.
塞西尔  拜托  确保詹娜的安全
Cecile, please, make sure that Jenna is safe.
-乔  我不会让...  -巴里
- Joe, I'm not gonna-- - Barry.
走  现在
Go...now.
好
Okay.
来  我们走
All right, come on. Let's go.
巴里
Barry!
我必须试试
I have to try.
我应该加入联邦证人保护计划
I should go into Witsec.
联邦探员随时会到
Federal Agent will be here anyminute.
他们会是仅有的知道你去哪的人
They'll be the only ones who know where you're going.
他们会保证你的安全  乔
They'll keep you safe, Joe,
至少到我们把卡夫这个麻烦处理掉
at least till we get this Carver mess sorted out.
感谢你  大卫  所有的一切  兄弟
Thank you, David, for everything, man.
爱瑞丝不接电话
Iris isn't answering her phone.
她需要知道这件事
She needs to know this is happening.
他们在这儿
They're here.
请告诉爱瑞丝我爱她  好吗
Just--just tell Iris I love her, okay?
我认为我做不到
Okay, I don't think I can do this.
-你可以的  -我不能
- Yes. Yes, you can. - I can't.
-不  我做不到  -听我说
- No, I can't. - Yes, listen.
这是保证我们家人安全的唯一途径
It's the only way to keep our family safe.
你就告诉小詹娜她的父亲会尽他所能
You just tell little baby Jenna that her daddy's gonna come home
很快回家的  好吗
as soon as he possibly can, okay?
我爱你  塞西尔·霍顿
I love you, Cecile Horton.
我爱你
I love you.
听  听我说
Listen, listen.
爱瑞丝和我  我们会打败卡夫和黑洞
Iris and I, we're gonna take down Carver and Black Hole.
然后我们就把你带回家
And then we're gonna bring you home.
我保证
I promise.
-保护好爱瑞丝  -我会的
- Keep Iris safe. - I will.
乔·韦斯特按你的要求不再碍事了
Joe West is out of the way as requested.
成功是无疑的
Success is assured.
很好
Good.
如果有人让我丈夫为他的行为付出代价
If anyone's gonna make my husband pay for what he did,
那一定是我
it's gonna be me.
看来乔·韦斯特队长不再是个问题了
Looks like Captain Joe West will no longer be a problem.
肯定还有别人也听到这则喜讯
Someone else must've heard the good news, too,
因为他们给你送了份礼物
because they sent you a gift.
我给你送过去了
I had it delivered.
你好  约瑟夫
Hello, Joseph.
你真是个难以取得联系的人
You're a hard man to get a hold of.
那是有意为之
That's on purpose.
等一下
Wait.
我只需要你的一个微不足道的东西
I just have one little thing I need from you...
一个道歉
an apology.
说真的吗
Seriously?
就是为了这个吗
That's what this is about?
我想要帮助这个世界
I wanted to help the world.
现在你在摧毁它
Now you're destroying it.
我在保证它的安全
I am keeping it safe.
你让我在这里等死
You let me rot in here
而你拿走了我创造的一切
while you took everything I created.
我对人类的未来有着愿景
I had a vision for humankind.
我也是
So did I!
而且现在我已经把它变为现实了
And now I'm making it a reality.
这是你最后一次机会了  约瑟夫
This is your last chance, Joseph.
真实的人才能被威胁  伊娃
Threats are for real people, Eva,
而不是幽灵  因为你现在就是
not phantoms, because that's what you are.
至于我
And me...
亲爱的
Darling...
我是触不可及的
I'm untouchable.
真正触不到
Literally.
我刚和大卫聊过
I just talked to David.
我爸真的走了吗
Is my dad really gone?
我试过给你打电话
I tried calling you.
这就是你的借口
That's your excuse?
我爸参加了证人保护计划  巴里
My dad is in witness protection, Barry.
你应该来找我
You should've come to get me.
是的  爱瑞丝  不过当时没有足够的时间
Yeah, Iris, there wasn't enough time.
你可是闪电侠啊  巴里
You're The Flash, Barry.
你可以把一秒变成一小时
You can make a second last an hour.
他在哪
Where is he?
我真的不知道
I-I honestly don't know.
那他什么时候会回来
When is he coming back?
等我们抓到卡夫的时候
The second that we catch Carver.
卡夫和那些政治家
Carver's pockets are lined with--
立法者有密切的利益往来  巴里
with politicians and lawmakers, Barry,
更不用提还有那些暗杀者了
not to mention assassins.
等我们抓到他可能要花上好几年时间
It could be years before we catch him.
爱瑞丝  我真的很抱歉  但塞西尔差点被杀
Iris, I'm so sorry, but Cecile was almost killed.
然后是乔
And then Joe.
他  他必须马上离开
He--he had to leave right away,
不然接下来卡夫可能会对付你或者詹娜
or else Carver may come after Jenna or you next.
卡夫已经在对付我了
Carver already came after me--
我当时也没有在场保护你
And I wasn't here to protect you.
听着  我只是想确保这个家的安全
Look, I'm--I'm--I'm trying to keep this family safe.
我想要你马上带我去见他
I want you to take me to him right now.
我告诉过你  我不知道他去哪了
I told you I don't know where he's going.
你不用知道  巴里
You don't need to, Barry.
他们离开了  可能大概只有三十分钟
They--they left, what, like 30 minutes ago?
他们很可能仍在八十公里半径范围内
They're probably still within a 50-mile radius.
凭借你的速度  几秒钟就能搜索完整个区域
With your speed, you can search that entire area in seconds.
你知道我做不到  再也不能了
You know I can't, not anymore.
是做不到  还是不想做
Can't or won't?
事情没那么简单
It's not that simple.
-是的  很简单  巴里  -不  并不是
- Yes, it is, Barry! - No, it isn't!
听着  爱瑞丝  我  我现在是在强撑着
Look, Iris, I'm-- I'm barely hanging on.
我感觉喘不上气
I can't catch my breath.
我觉得头晕  我的脚也麻了
I'm getting dizzy. My feet are numb.
我的手指感到刺痛
My fingers tingle.
我每走一步都感觉好像
It feels like with every step I take,
自己要被撕成两半了
I'm getting ripped in two.
我现在想的都是  如果我明天可以足够快
All I can think about is if I'll be fast enough
我就能救下另一条生命
tomorrow to save another life.
我相信过你  巴里
I trusted you, Barry.
爱瑞丝...
Iris...
现在我们有了另一个共同点
Now we have something else in common.
我们都失去了自己的父母
We both lost our parents.
希望他们都不是白白离开的
I hope that was worth it.
你要去哪  爱瑞丝
Where are you going? Iris.
我想要你离开
I want you to leave.
-你不是认真的吧  -巴里  你总是这么做
- You can't be serious. - Barry, you always do this.
你总是做完了所有选择
You always make all of these decisions,
然后让我们剩下的人来为你收拾残局
and then the rest of us have to deal with the fallout.
闪点  进入神速力
Flashpoint, going into the Speed Force,
带诺拉去未来  还有这次的事
taking Nora into the future, and now this--
-我受够了  巴里  -爱瑞丝...
- I am done, Barry. - Iris...
我要你出去
I want you to get out.
求你了
Please.
好吧  听着  我们可以解决的
Okay, look, we can work through this.
-你就是我的家  -不再是了
- You're my home. - Not anymore.
走
Leave.